片名：異變
大西洋 深度16000英尺
三大洋礦業集團
任務:採集銀礦及其他研究
任務等級:極度危險
四號礦坑,14號貨櫃準備吊起
Four to shack. Container 14 ready to winch.
六號礦坑,采銀工作完成
Six to shack. Silver extraction completed.
開採礦坑7號 居住與工作場所 90天已過87天
六號礦坑,采銀工作完成
Six to shack. Silver extraction completed.
開採礦坑7號 居住與工作場所 90天已過87天
這些食物不錯,墨式卷餅,玉米餡餅...
That's good eating. Burritos, enchiladas...
- 黑豆和米飯,夥計.這是波多黎各人吃的 - 嘿, 我會帶你去波多黎各...
Black beans and rice, man. That's Puerto Rican. Hey, I gotta take you...
好吧,我不想打斷你們對偉大的拉丁美食的討論
Well, I hate to break up the great Latino gourmet debate...
但我們還沒下班呢，所以...
but we ain't off the clock yet, so uh...
自從我們在這有段日子了
Since we got a few more days here, can somebody...
有人能告訴我，誰是吊櫃員嗎?
please tell me who the hook is?
15號,是你嗎?
Fifteen, is that you?
是你吊的22號貨櫃嗎?
You got a hook on box 22?
有人在問你，是你吊的22號貨櫃嗎？你這蠢貨
The man is asking you if you're hooked on 22, you dumb shit.
注意你的語氣,希克斯派克 15號呼叫礦坑
Watch your mouth, Sixpack. Fifteen to shack.
我是鐘斯，我不是吊櫃員
This is Jones. I ain't the hook.
7號呼叫礦坑，我是吊櫃員
Seven to shack. I'm the hook.
好的,吊起22號貨櫃然後下班
Okay there, seven. Pack up box 22 and call it a day.
威莉,你怎麼了?我們在等你
Hey, Willie, you trip on a tit or something? We're all waitin' on ya honey.
別廢話，希克斯派克
Go suck on a shrimp, Sixpack.
七號呼叫礦坑,準備吊起
Seven to shack. Ready to winch.
好的,吊起
There we go. Winch on.
各位,下班回家吧
Okay, miners, let's come on home.
你聽到他說的了？我們走吧
You heard the man. Let's get movin' folks.
來吧,夥計們，我們還有三天就要離開這了
Come on, guys. We only have three days left.
我聽到了
I hear that.
貝克，燒好水，我們要回來了
Put the kettle on, Beck. We're coming home.
醫生出去了
好的，醫生， 事情不如你所見的
Well, Doc, not so as you'd notice
從早到日落
but the sun has set on yet another day
在家園辛勤勞動了一整天
of hard labor and toil here at the homestead.
挖到16噸，你又得到了什麼？
Sixteen tons and what do you get.
日漸老去，還深陷債務
Another day older and deeper in debt
聖彼得啊, 別召喚我，因為我還不能去
Saint Peter, don't you call me 'cause I can't go
我還欠公司一條命
I owe my soul to the company store.
鐘斯! 幫我下!
Jonesy! Help!
柯布!
Cobb!
我的呼吸器停止運行了，我正在失去壓力
My rebreather's stopped! I'm losing compression!
我的潛水服要爆裂了 醫生! 貝克!
I'm gonna blow my suit! Doc! Beck!
我聽到了,從這堿搢繭L不妥
Yeah, I got you, DeJesus. You look fine from in here.
- 把情況告訴我 - 我的呼吸器停了!
- Give me a readout. - My rebreather's stopped!
我正在失去壓力 無法呼吸
I'm losing compression! I can't breathe!
德休斯先生, 我不能...
Mr. DeJesus, I can't...
如果你這樣驚慌失措,我就無法獲知情況
I can't get an accurate readout if you panic.
醫生,是急事,出麻煩了,速來
Doc, we got an emergency here. We need you. Got trouble.
醫生! 醫生!
Doc! Doc!
慢慢用鼻吸氣...
So just breathe slowly and through your nose and uh...
用口呼氣
and out through your mouth.
我認為你只是呼吸過速
I think you're hyperventilating.
- 呼吸過速, 才不是呢! - 你怎麼做的??
- Hyperventilating, my ass! - How do you do this?
- 他會爆炸的 - 不,他不會爆炸
- He's gonna blow. - No, he's not gonna blow!
醫生! 貝克!
(coughing) Doc! Beck!
- 救命! - 醫生, 快來!
- Help! - Doc, come on!
- 查看他的氧氣存量 - 我在查
- Check his oxygen level. - Yeah, I'm doin' that.
- 想辦法, 快點! - 我在想
- Do something, quick! - I'm doin' it.
救命!
Help!
該死!
Damn!
把他接往RV四號接駁器.
Hook him to my RV-four transpac.
好的,把他接往...
Right. Hook him to the RV...
不,別這樣做! 不要包圍他
No! Don't do that! Don't circumventilate him.
我想他在冒內爆的危險
I think you're risking an implosion probability.
醫生,我們需要你 把他送來礦坑
Doc, we need you. Bring him into the shack.
- 時間不夠！ - 還有時間,照做吧
- There's not enough time! - You've got time. Just do it.
我會沒命的！
I'm gonna die!
你不會死的
You ain't gonna die.
繼續讓他移動
Just keep him moving.
小心點！我們可以安然無恙的
Take it easy. We'll make it. We'll make it.
打開這該死的門
Open the damn door.
快來,救他進去
Come on! Get him inside!
保持移動
Keep him moving.
把鎖拉起
Come on, lift lock. Go.
來吧，把鎖拉起來
Come on, lift lock. Up.
呼吸器，沒氣泡的東西不能信任
Rebreathers. I don't trust anything that doesn't have bubbles comin' out of it.
不是那該死的潛水衣，夥計 是貝克
It ain't the goddamn suit, man. It's Beck.
不是他的錯 醫生該在場的
It's not his fault. Doc should've been there.
若他真的有麻煩,醫生會在場
If he was a real shack boss, Doc would have been there.
這次是他走運
He got real lucky this time.
嗨！今天華爾街指數衝破了15000點
Hey, Wall Street broke the 15,000-point barrier today.
見鬼！我的獎金
Shit. There goes my bonus.
你知道嗎,我遇過海底爆炸的人
You know, I stood next to a guy who blew a suit once.
當時在印度洋,我來告訴你孩子，那情形很可怕
He was in the Indian Ocean. Boy, I'm telling you that is not a pretty sight.
嘿，別打擾他
Hey, leave Hazy alone, man.
潛水衣上就這麼一個小孔
One tiny little hole in the fucking toe of his suit man.
不會比你的小弟弟大
No bigger than your click.
沒錯，孩子！海水都湧了進去
Yeah, boy, that ocean came in.
壓力使他整個人的軀體都被擠進了頭盔
The pressure just crammed his whole body up into his helmet.
我們只能埋葬了他的頭盔
We just buried his helmet.
- 那個人可能會是你, 德休斯 - 我知道什麼是內爆
- That would've been you, DeJesus. - Hey, I know about implosion.
對，你的褲子大概會爆炸
Yeah, I bet you do. I bet you was imploding in your pants.
- 別再說了, 礦坑! - 住手吧，夥計們
- Knock it off, Sixpack! - Cut it out, you guys.
我們被困在這個坑堣w經好長段日子了
We've been stuck down in this hole for a hell of a long time
關係密切，不能因這麼小的事情就內訌
and we had a close call. We're not gonna let something like this break us apart.
醫生由我負責
The doc is my responsibility.
醫生由我負責？
廢話
Bullshit.
(Groaning and creaking)
天哪，我只希望有運氣能完成這兩個月來在2英里深的海底下的工作
God, it would be just my luck to finish two months' worth of work two miles under
還剩三天這地方就要崩潰了
and have the whole place fall apart with just three days left.
- 有誰查了海面的天氣如何？ - 是的
- Anyone check weather up top? - Yeah.
只是雨,但接送時會晴朗
It's raining, but it's supposed to be clear for pickup.
只要沒浪便成,我討厭海浪
As long as there's no waves. I hate waves.
海浪是最糟糕的，你知道如果你回到水面會做什麼嗎？?
Waves my ass. Do you know what you'd be doin' if you were up top right now?
- 喝酒玩女人 - 噢,礦坑!
- Drinkin' brew and eatin' pussy. - Oh, Sixpack!
- 交通堵塞如何？ - 見怪不怪
- How about gettin' stuck in traffic? - Hey, wherever I can find it.
我來告訴你，你會做些什麼
I'll tell you what you'd be doing.
看著電視上令人作嘔的新聞
Be watching news on TV that's so bad, it makes you nauseous.
實在太糟糕了，你想駕車去呼吸新鮮空氣
So bad that you get in your car to get some fresh air
沒過5分鐘，你意識到
and after five minutes, you realize
空氣太污濁,叫你無法呼吸
the air's so dirty, you can't breathe.
如果你運氣好，你能回到家
If you're lucky enough to get back to your house...
你看著與別人無兩樣的屋子
that looks the same as everybody else's...
你發現老婆和以前一樣肥胖
you find that your wife is as fat as she ever was.
孩子沒因吸毒而使身體瘦弱
And the only reason your kids aren't strung out on the drugs
是因他們吸食新的毒品
they were using is because they've found some new drugs
而這堿O個好地方
which screw 'em up even more, and that's just the good part.
你們竟不知在這埵釵h幸福
You people just don't appreciate how good you've got it down here.
- 別讓我打攪你們,柯布先生 - 沒關係,我剛講完
- Don't let me interrupt you, Mr. Cobb. - That's all right, sir. I was just finished.
- 你感覺怎樣？, 德休斯? - 我沒事
- How are you feeling there, DeJesus? - I'm okay.
- 見過醫生沒有？ - 沒有
- See the doc yet? - No.
晚餐後最好給醫生看看
Well, you better let the doc take a look at you after dinner.
- 先前他很忙 - 當我們需要他時卻沒空
- Since he was busy earlier. - When we needed him.
你為什麼不讓我來對付醫生
Why don't you let me handle the doc.
這已使我感到好過些了
Makes me feel better already.
我在看…礦坑多時沒人保養
I was looking at the shack maintenance hours outstanding.
我知是怎麼回事
I see where this is going.
我們都沒時間維修礦坑
Well, um, see, all of us owe some shack maintenance time.
今晚是動手維修的好時刻
I thought tonight would be a good time to get it done.
沒門，貝克先生，今晚不行
No way, Mr. Beck. No bleepin' way.
我們剛輪班完畢
We just pulled a full shift.
你不能再回礦坑堣u作
You can't call shack duty on top of a full shift.
這有違工會規定,合同上寫清的
That's a union violation. It's in the contract.
說得對, 柯布 讓我們聽聽工人代表有什麼話說
Right on, Cobb. Let's hear it for the shop steward.
喔!
Woo!
你聽到嗎, 貝克? 公司要依規矩辦事
Hear that, Becky? The company's got to abide by the rules.
我知道合同上怎麼寫, 柯布先生, 問題是你可依合同辦事
I know about the contract, Mr. Cobb, and the deal is you can follow the letter
也可多花一工作日把任務完成
of the contract to the law and you can spend an extra workday gettin' it done
也可今晚把它做完,明天休息
or you can get it done tonight and call tomorrow a down day.
- 你讓我們休息放假？ - 是的
- What, are you giving us the day off? - Looks that way.
我們的指標怎麼樣了？
What about our quota?
我們離指標只差25噸
You're only 25 tons off quota.
我們在最後一天會超額完成
You're bound to go way over that by the last day.
只是放一天假,對我來說沒分別
Look, folks, it's just a day off. It don't make no difference to me.
只看你們的意思,我以為是好事
It's just up to you. I thought it might be good.
- 我想放一天假 - 我也想
- Hell, I could use a day off. - Me too.
- 管他呢 - 好，有三個人贊成了
- What the hell. - Okay, shop steward's three.
- 四個 - 四個？還有麼？
- Four. - Four. Anybody else?
- 六個 - 好極了, 這就是我們要的
- Six. - All right, here's what we got.
柯布先生, 氣閘那不斷有聲響
Mr. Cobb, we still got that rattle in the air duct Somewhere.
- 去查看下 - 好
- Take a look at that. - Okay.
威莉,你檢查下德休斯的潛水衣
Williams, run a diagnostic on DeJesus' suit.
- 還有誰的潛水衣有問題？ - 我的袋子有問題
- Anybody else got any suit problems? - Yeah, my pocket.
你能檢查下我的口袋嗎，甜心？
Can you check my pocket, sweetheart?
晚安,我叫湯普生,單身
Good evening. Name's Thompson. Party of one.
我訂了桌子八點十五分 別太靠近樂隊，拜託
My reservation was 8:15. Not too near the Orchestra, please.
你明天會上班嗎，醫生?
Are you gonna come to work tomorrow, Doc?
我明早要上高爾夫球課
Well, I'll be on the golf course in the morning.
如果沒什麼意外
Then, if I don't have any babies to deliver
午餐後我回來
I could stop by after lunch.
今天我們差點出意外 德休斯的潛水衣
We almost had an accident today. DeJesus's suit.
你有什麼話對我說嗎？
You have something to say to me?
是的
Yeah. Section 1412
海洋操作手冊1412段寫明
of the Tri-Oceanic manual requires
在外面操作時控制室
a mining shack's medical officer to be present in the control room
需要有一醫護人員當值
during all exterior operations.
我只想向你說清楚這點
I just wanna make real damn sure that's clear.
好吧,我明天只打九個洞
I'll keep it to nine holes in the morning.
多謝你處理這情況
Thank you, sir, for taking care of that situation.
- 該死的,你聽聽 - 那只是老化了而已
- Listen to it, for Christ's sake. - It's just gettin' old, that's all.
不能每次有聲響便要拆這地方
You don't see Doc opening me up every time my joints start to creak.
只是空氣迴圈，讓它去吧，來吧
As long as it's recycling the air, let it be. Come on.
十賠一 是短路
Ten to one it's a short.
好吧
Okay-
輕而易舉
Piece of cake.
好極了
Great.
好一對寶貨
Oh, mama! What a pair.
你說什麼？
What'd you say?
我說一對活寶
I said, "What a pair."
我們的礦坑主管和他的醫生朋友
Our shack boss and his washed-up doctor buddy make quite a...
- 你以為我說什麼？ - 說你喜歡我的大胸
- What did you think I said? - That you liked my boobs.
(Machine rattling)
你留心看我老柯布的手段吧，行不？
You watch the old Cobb magic, all right?
褒曼的心意
Compliments of Bowman.
(Rattling quiets down)
耶
Yeah.
你怎麼做到的？
How in the hell did you do that?
別對任何人說,這是商業機密
You don't say anything to anybody. Job security.
好不好?走吧
All right? Let's go.
慢著,你是怎麼辦到的？
Now, wait a minute, man. How in the hell did you do that?
沒什麼
That's clean.
但好像有什麼不對勁 啊,天哪
But there's nothing wrong with it. Oh, my God!
過來,九鬼
Come here, Kuki.
這,九鬼
Here, Kuki.
希克斯派克, 你個臭狗屎!
Sixpack, you shit!
驚喜吧!
Surprise!
我們會從礦坑采到多少銀？
How much silver are we gonna start taking out of that mine again?
就好像, 我來告訴你，瑪蒂, 你找到了個如假包換的
Well, it's like I tell you, Martin, I think you've got an honest-to-God
大富礦
bonanza on your hands.
幾天塈A就能把我們拉回去，這礦多的是
You can haul us out in a couple of days. This mine will play itself.
等我通知大西洋業務的主管
When I told the Director of Atlantic Operations
要安排地質學家來這堮...
that we had to stick a geologist down there and turn that mine around...
我不知道你會證明我是個天才
I had no idea that you were going to prove me a genius.
- 好吧，有你的關心我就很高興了，瑪蒂 - 我太激動了
- Well, I'm glad you're happy, Martin. - I'm ecstatic.
我等不及離開這兒
'Cause I can't wait to get the fuck outta here.
什麼？
What?
我等不及再次做探險潛水
I said, I really can't wait to get back to exploration diving.
我多渴望研究...
I miss the research, and...
還有,我查過那湯普生醫生了
By the way, I ran that check on Dr. Thompson.
他除有幾次不服從指令外
He has a few incidences of insubordination
他的資歷很不錯
but his credentials are very impressive.
他讀醫理學,發明了幾種疫苗…
Pharmacology. He pioneered several vaccines.
這堣S不是梅約醫學中心 他為什麼會來這堙A瑪蒂？
Well, this ain't the Mayo Clinic. How'd he get down here, Martin?
他發明的血清害死了幾個人
A serum he developed killed several people.
那是意外,就是比例不對
An accident, but it got blown all out of proportion.
你看, 貝克
Now, look, Beck.
現在事情進展很順利
Things are beginning to move very fast now.
若他有麻煩,獲你需要幫忙…
If you're having a problem with him or you need any help...
只管說好了
just say the word.
用不著
No.
事情我還可以應付
No, I don't think it's anything I can't handle.
好的
Good.
你的股票如何？ 還沒賺到一百萬？
How are your stocks doin'? Haven't you made your million yet?
還沒有
Not yet.
- 三大洋公司的股票如何，夥計？ - 這兒有錢嗎？
- How's Tri-Oceanic doing, Bow? - Got money in this tub?
我簽了股票期權
Yeah. I signed up for the stock option.
去年他們失去一艘油輪後
You know, last year when they lost a tanker,
股票跌破了底價,我損失慘重
the bottom fell out of their stock and I lost a bloody fortune.
你把錢看得太認真了
You take your money too seriously.
(Structure groaning and creaking)
你說的對,我到這堥茖瓣ㄛO玩樂的
You're damn right, I do. I'm not down here for fun.
說誰玩樂？
Fun? Somebody talkin' fun?
看看那雙雪白的腿
(Wolf whistle)
Whew, look at those white legs!
嘿,威莉,寶貝,今晚的事很抱歉
Hey, Willie, honey, I'm sorry about that little incident tonight.
我以為開個小玩笑可以輕鬆一點
You know, I just thought a little humor might loosen things up.
小心, 希克斯派克!
Hey, watch it, Sixpack!
請別見怪
No hard feelings?
不會
Nope. Sweet dreams.
我佳人有約
I got a date with an angel.
來吧,寶貝
Come on, baby.
坐在我的臉上
Sit on my face.
(Screaming)
該死的, 威莉,你這婊子
Goddamn it, Williams! You bitch!
你個賤人, 你看看我的腳！ 你看看我的腳！
You bitch, look at my foot! Look at my goddamn foot!
- 我還以為你覺得這很有趣 - 有趣？
- I thought you'd find that funny. - You think it's funny?
你把這個吃了便不會覺得有趣的了
You're gonna think it's funny when you eat this goddamn thing!
- 這兒到底發生了什麼事？ - 看看我的腳
- What the hell's goin' on here? - Look at my foot!
這婊子把海怪放在我的床鋪上
This bitch put a goddamn sea monster in my bunk!
- 你怎知道是她幹的？ - 就是她，該死!
- How do you know it was her? - Lt was her, goddammit!
- 你是說我撒謊嗎, 貝克? - 可能有這麼大
- Are you calling me a liar, Beck? - That may be the size of it, Bubba.
- 你和威莉明天不用出海執勤 - 見鬼！
- You and Williams just pulled sea duty tomorrow. - Oh, bullshit!
老天！你們別吵好嗎？
Oh, geez! Will you pipe down?
取消半天假,若再胡鬧,全天取消
You just got half a day. Any more hoopla, it's a full one.
準備練習
Ready to drill.
看來是不錯的礦脈,炸了它
Looks like a nice vein of ore.
- 好,炸了它 - 好的
- Let's blow it. - Blow this.
起爆
Charge activated.
嗨，威莉，有使你想起什麼嗎？
Hey, Willie, remind you of anything?
哈哈哈
Ha, ha, ha.
哇
Oh, yeah!
看來是個大礦床
It looks like the mother load, guys.
這埵A亮點
I need more light on that, seven.
希克斯派克,聽到了嗎？我們要再多一點照明
Sixpack, you hear that? We need more light.
希克斯派克? 希克斯派克?
Sixpack? Sixpack?
好了
All right, look.
線纜卡住了
The cable's stuck.
(Screaming)
希克斯派克. 希克斯派克, 出了什麼事?
Sixpack. Sixpack, what's happened?
我們沒他的信號了
We've lost him.
你們做什麼？開派對嗎？, 希克斯派克?
Well, what are you doing? Having a party out there, Sixpack?
貝克,我正在找他
Beck, I'm looking for him.
礦坑呼叫七號 外面發生什麼事？, 威莉?
Shack to seven. What's going on out there, Williams?
他不見了
He's gone.
威莉, 跟我通話,發生了什麼事？
Williams, speak to me. What's happening out there?
希克斯派克. 希克斯派克, 回答我
Sixpack. Sixpack, answer.
我的天
Oh, my God!
威莉
Williams!
快點,威莉，後備的波段是哪個？
Come on, Williams. What's the alternate?
試試35波段
Try 35.
威莉? 是她
Williams? There she is.
威莉,你聽到了嗎？發生什麼事了？
Williams, you hear me? What's going on out there?
天,他掉進南山脊去了
God, he's gone over the South Ridge.
我要下去找他
I'm going down after him.
自己當心,我們不知道那下面有些什麼
Watch yourself, 'cause we don't know what the hell is off that ridge.
來吧, 德休斯, 加油
Come on, Jonesy, work it out.
- 希克斯派克失蹤了! - 他們沒綁好安全繩嗎？
- Sixpack's lost! - Weren't they tied?
- 不知道,他不見了 - 他們該是綁好的
- I don't know, he's lost! - They're supposed to be tied.
- 來吧，我們走 - 走吧
- Come on. Let's go. - Move it!
老天！
Oh, God!
有什麼發現？
What've we got?
- 管蠕蟲 - 她怎麼脫身？
- Tube worms. - How's she gonna get out of there?
褒曼, 那衣服的空氣容量可維持多久？
Bowman, what's the self-contained air capacity of that suit?
三十分鐘
Thirty minutes.
六號呼叫礦坑
(Heavy radio interference) This is six to shack.
Six to shack.
是希克斯派克
Sixpack.
上帝啊, 為什麼他的閃燈不亮？
For God's sakes, why doesn't Sixpack have his blinkers on?
他可能就在附近,但她看不見他
The man could be two feet away and on fire and she wouldn't see him.
什麼?
What?
這是什麼東西？
What is this?
一艘船?
A ship?
這是俄文
That's Russian.
你們看到了嗎？
Are you picking this up?
是的,我們看到了,七號！ 你能把那畫面再給我們看下嗎?
Yeah, we got it, Seven. Can you open up that picture a little for us?
利維坦
Leviathan.
- 什麼? - 利維坦
- What? - Leviathan.
- 褒曼, 去查查 - 好的
- Bowman, run a check. - Sir.
- 威莉, 你的空氣存量好有多少？ - 二十分鐘
- Williams, What's your air reading? - Twenty minutes.
五分鐘後我們就來救你
We're gonna give you five, then we're coming in.
鐘斯, 柯布, 穿潛水衣
Jones, Cobb, suit up.
我要進去了
I'm going inside.
希克斯派克
Sixpack.
國際船隻註冊記錄  船名：利維坦   搜索中
希克斯派克, 回答我!
Sixpack, answer me!
國際船隻註冊記錄  船名：利維坦   搜索中
希克斯派克, 回答我!
Sixpack, answer me!
波羅地海?
Baltic Sea?
你在那發現什麼, 褒曼?
What have you got there, Bowman?
利維坦號，波羅地海的俄國客船
The Leviathan. Currently with the Russian Fleet in the Baltic Sea.
現在它就像堆馬糞，爛鐵
Currently horseshit. Currently it's rusted junk, and we're lookin' at it.
肯定搞錯了,一定是輸入資料不對
Well, it's gotta be wrong. Maybe you didn't enter it correctly.
這媦g著:波羅地海
It's right here. The Baltic Sea.
也許船沉了,他們沒留意它失蹤
Maybe a ship sinks and they don't notice it's missing.
威莉,你還有一分鐘來找到希克斯派克並及離開現場
Williams, you got one minute to find Sixpack and get your butt out of there.
如果威莉還有一分鐘，那希克斯派克還有多少時間？
If Willie's got a minute, how much time does Sixpack have?
醫務室
The infirmary.
哇!
Whoooo!
我發財了, 寶貝!
I'm rich, honey!
我發財了
I'm rich!
安全失誤? 我一個字都聽不到
Safety negligence? I never even heard a word.
如果我聽不到又怎能報告？
How can I be on report if I never even heard a word?
我說得對不, 柯布?
Ain't that right, Cobby?
別廢話！這次你自我開脫好了, 希克斯派克.
Don't Cobby me. You're on your own this time, Sixpack.
你折騰了大家一天的時間
You almost fucked up everybody's day.
是只手錶,還在走
A Timex. And it's still ticking.
俄國盧布,看來錢不多
A little Russian money. It don't look like much.
這埵釭F西給你
Here's something for you, Bow.
嘿, 希克斯派克,看看你的女朋友
Hey, Sixpack, look at your girlfriends.
哎!
Whew!
- 那是什麼？ - "吉蒂愛基夫"
- What's that? - "Kitty Does Kiev."
- 很黃，很配你 - 讓我看看
- Porn. Right up your alley. - Let me see that.
是俄文,我不知道是什麼意思
It's in Russian. I don't know what it says.
- 能讓我看下嗎? - 醫生,那不是盤黃色錄影帶
- May I see it, please? - Doc, it's not really "Kitty Does Kiev."
- 是船長日誌的錄影帶 - 別告訴我你懂俄語
- It's the captain's log on videotape. - Don't tell me you read Russian.
我會俄語，德語，義大利語，法語
Russian, German, Italian, Spanish,
還會點斯瓦希婸y和零星的印地語
French, a little Swahili and a smattering of Hindi.
- 是我修讀醫科時的部分課程 - 吹牛
- It's part of my premed background. - Bullshit.
那你會相信個俄國老奶奶嗎？
Would you believe a Russian grandmother?
那我相信
That I believe.
- 這是什麼？ - 是個人物品,醫生，你能念下這嗎?
- What's this? - Personal effects, Doc. Can you read that?
死了
Deceased.
這是怎麼回事?
What's all this?
死了
Deceased.
他們都死了
Deceased. All of them.
- 柯布先生,把這兒的事辦好 - 好的
- Mr. Cobb, wrap all that up. - Right.
德休斯, 把最後一個箱子倒出來
DeJesus, dump this last box.
- 那太可惜了 -是什麼？ - 是伏特加
That's nice. What is this? Vodka.
還是名牌酒
Stresnavga. Hey, that's good stuff.
可以用來開完工慶祝派對
Make for a great end-of-shift party.
嗨,貝克,如果你舉報我,這瓶酒就歸我
Hey, Becky, if I'm on report, I guess this bottle's mine, huh?
好吧，你說得對,就是你的
Well, I guess you're right. It is yours.
但這是偷竊,你違反了兩項安全守則
But it's pilferage, so now you're down for two counts of safety negligence
擅自上船，還危及威莉的性命
for risking Williams's life, going on that boat and possessing
以及擁有違禁品
restricted material.
- 柯布先生, 但所有的均遭沒收了 - 是這樣
- Mr. Cobb, all this gets impounded. - It's done.
還有一件事
And one more thing.
如果你再叫我一次“貝基”, 希克斯派克
I think if I hear you call me "Becky" one more time, Sixpack,
我就宰了你...我來真的
I'm gonna pop your tops... all six of 'em.
(Speaking in Russian)
我的醫務室住滿了人
My infirmary's filled.
隨船醫生告訴我，就像傳染病
The doctors on board tell me it's like a tropical infection.
(Speaking in Russian)
這情況是前所未見的
But it's not like anything I've ever seen before.
此外還有一事是我不明白的
And there's something else I don't understand.
他們都完了
And then it goes off.
那麼你想對我說些什麼, 醫生? 此事太詭異了
OK. So what do you want me to say, Doc? It all sounds mysterious?
是
Yea.
他為什麼捨棄了他的日誌記錄?
Well, why did he leave his log tape?
為什麼會有2艘相同船名的船在不同的地方?
Why are there two ships with the same name in different places?
我怎麼知道,是你懂俄語,也許你搞錯了？
Hell, I don't know. You read Russian. Maybe you read it wrong.
我沒有,即使我誤會了意思
I didn't. Even if I had, there should be a record of some ship that's
也許有記錄說這埵囧膜漲陴謒I了,但卻沒有記錄
sunk within 100 miles of here, and there's not.
你來看看,船殼有洞
And look at this tear. This hole in the hull.
這是爆炸的後果，我認為這是遭魚雷擊中
That's the result of an explosion. I think that was a torpedo hit.
我認為這艘船是被蓄意弄沉的
I think that ship was sunk on purpose.
嘿，醫生,你怎麼知道那是遭魚雷擊中？
Hey Doc, now how the hell do you know that's a torpedo hit?
我意思是,和另一艘船相撞也會有洞
I mean, a collision with another boat could produce that hole.
我不同意你的觀點
I don't agree with you.
- 相撞產生的洞不會這麼參差不齊... - 那是怎麼回事?
- This hole would not be so jagged... - So what?
我是說，那麼他們為什麼要弄沉自己的船?
I mean, so what if they scuttle their own boat?
我可不會離開自己的船
I can't get bent outta shape just because some people
就這樣把船員留在海底任其死去腐爛
got some jungle rot and ended up dead on a barge on the bottom of the ocean.
我瞭解石塊，我瞭解礦石, 醫生 但我不瞭解俄國人的船
I know about rocks. I know about stones, Doc. I don't know about Russian boats.
好吧，我和你賭5塊錢，這是筆誤
Plus which, I bet you five dollars it's a clerical error.
見鬼去吧,我們有什麼疑問，就讓海事部門的人去搞清楚吧
Hell, we sounded the horn on it. Let the maritime people figure it out.
我得去把升降機修好
I gotta fix the lift lock.
還剩兩天
Okay, two more days.
別節外生枝了
Let's have no waves.
天氣系統上線，追測氣候變化
Weather system on line. Tracking meteorological patterns.
- 開始掃描 - 我討厭...
- Beginning scan. - I hate...
海浪
waves.
嗨， 柯布
Hey, Cobb.
你知道瑞士人說四種語言嗎?
You know that in Switzerland, they speak four major languages?
- 我才不關心 - 我關心
- Ask me if I care. - I do.
離開這堳嵺瓻K去瑞士
When I get outta here, I'm goin' there.
我要找間漂亮的，白雪覆蓋的小屋……
I'm gonna find a nice snow-covered chalet...
熱情的女子，熊熊爐火，還有滑雪
warm little woman, crackling fire, and ski.
嘿, 柯布,如果你像這樣
Hey, Cobb, if you're gonna be doing that, man,
你要穿上沙灘褲去海灘
you should be wearing what you wear to the beach.
我討厭海灘
I hate the beach.
你看我找到什麼
Hey, guys. Look what I got.
- 真想不到,你查到了 - 對，來親一下
- I don't believe it. You got 'em. - Yeah, put it there.
怎麼回事，怎會是貝克的資料
What are you doing with Beck's personnel records?
注意看，你就明白了
Watch. You'll see.
Four, zero, five, four
eight, six.
你們這些人真是胡說八道,你以為他真的笨？
You guys are so full of shit. I mean, how stupid do you think he is?
有誰會用社會福利號？
Who's gonna use their social security number?
行了
Bingo!
就是我的了
That bottle's mine.
- 聰明, 德休斯，樣本杯? - 別緊張
- Cute, DeJesus. Specimen cups? - Hey, loosen up, Bow.
- 嘿，威莉，倒了一杯給你 - 我不要了,謝謝
- Hey, Willie, got one poured for you. - Not for me, thanks.
你要運動下，來吧，你該享受下了
All you do is exercise. Come on, you gotta live a little.
兩天塈畯n接受宇航員訓練
My astronaut training starts in two days.
算了吧，我替她喝
Forget space cadet. I'll drink hers.
若他回來發覺酒不見了怎辦？
What happens if he goes back and finds the bottle missing?
他不會的，我把伏特加放在這兒
He won't. I put the vodka in here.
機靈鬼
Smart lad.
乾杯
Cheers.
- 是水 - 貝克給換掉了
- It's water. - Beck switched it.
那鬼傢伙信不過我們
That son of a gun doesn't trust us.
那個滑頭，我要好好修理他
That pretty-boy little turd. I'm gonna fix his ass.
- 我們的派對泡了湯 - 不壞
- There goes our party. - It's not bad.
- 真的不錯 - 是水
- It's not bad at all. - It's water.
嗨
Hi!
我說過喜歡喝伏特加嗎？
Did I tell you vodka's my favorite drink?
(Groaning and creaking)
Whoa.
這是個龐然大物
That was a pretty big one, huh?
- 我們現在該適應吧 - 對
- You'd think we'd get used to it by now. - Yeah.
你在浪費時間,要完全關閉並詳細檢查
You're wasting your time here. This needs a shutdown and an overhaul.
是, 我需要詳細檢查 訓練進行如何？
Yeah, I need an overhaul. How's the training goin'?
很順利
It's going well.
相信我做得不錯
I think I've got a good shot.
我只希望別人別為難我
I just wish everyone would stop giving me a hard time.
是啊，我明白你的意思
Yeah, I know what you mean.
你來幫我按鈕吧
Why don't you give me a hand and hit that button, huh?
- 按D，L鍵 - 什麼?
- Push D.L. - What?
D和L
D.L.
哦，夥計
Oh, man.
你來這兒幹嗎？
What are you doing down here?
我來這想修下升降機的鎖
Well, I'm trying to fix this short in the lift lock.
你來這兒幹什麼？威莉?
What are you doing down here, Williams?
- 你明白我的意思 - 是的,我明白
- You know what I mean. - Yeah, I know what you mean.
- 你不該來這礦坑的 - 你說得對
- You don't belong in a mine. - You got that right.
有人出了個好主意
But somebody just got the brilliant idea
把地質學家派來這兒管理你們這群鄉巴佬
to stick a geologist down here in charge of you cowboys.
也許他們認為我勝任
I think maybe they thought that just 'cause I could tell
該死的銀礦，我只知道怎樣運行這個地方
shit from silver, I'd know how to run this place.
你是麼？
Well, do you?
你說呢？
You tell me.
我認為你處理德休斯的方法很好
I think you handled DeJesus pretty well.
是嘛?
Yeah?
只是走運而已,我都嚇得要死
Well, that was luck. I was scared to death.
希克斯派克怎麼樣了?
What about Sixpack?
他怎麼了？
What about him?
你會因為我而罰他嗎？
Did you bust him because of me?
可能吧
Maybe.
很感激你,但我沒事
Well, I appreciate that. But I'm okay.
我知道
Yeah, I know.
好
Good.
話說回來,你怎知他們打伏特加的注意？
Oh, by the way, how did you know they'd get into the vodka?
換了是我也會這麼做
Hell, that's what I would've done.
也許我們是英雄所做略同
Maybe you're more one of us than you think.
早安
Good morning.
對不起
Sorry.
好的
Okay. That's good.
只管看著我的前額
Just look at my forehead.
對了
That's it.
給我看看舌頭
Let me see your tongue.
早安,各位 有什麼不妥嗎, 醫生?
Good morning, gentlemen. What's wrong, Doc?
看來就是點宿醉
I'm getting a pretty good imitation of a hangover.
- 脫下襯衣 - 那不是宿醉
- Take off your shirt. - Lt ain't no hangover.
感覺要嚴重千倍
Feels about 1000 times worse.
這些瘀痕有了多久？
How long did you have these spots?
- 什麼 - 別碰它們
- What? - Don't touch it.
好吧，作為礦坑的主管,由你決定
Well, as First Officer of the shack, it's your call.
換了我,便不會倉促行事
But if I were you, I'd not be too hasty.
我不明白
I don't get it.
在既定離開時間提前一天撤退
Any evacuation 24 hours before a scheduled pickup
或多或少對良好的記錄有影響
won't look good on an otherwise excellent record.
但一如我說,由你決定
But like I said, it's your call.
沒有他掉下去
Well, as bad as he is, there's no way
我們是無法完成指標的
we're gonna make that quota without his sad self down there.
- 他幫了我們 - 不，我不這麼想
- He's tankin' on us. - No, I don't think so.
昨晚他語氣不太好
I heard him last night, and he didn't sound so good.
公司看到數字時會考慮到這點
The company will take that under consideration when they look at our numbers.
親愛的，公司才不管個中原因
Sweetheart, the company doesn't give a damn about why.
合同上說如果我們無法完成指標
The contract says, if we miss our quota
他們只會付給我們一半酬金
they only gotta pay us half pay for the entire month.
我相信他們肯定會這樣做
Believe me, they'll stick to it.
那傢伙真的是幫了我們
The bastard's definitely tanking on us.
- 我認為你說得對 - 但願他是,可是他又不是
- Yep, I think you're right. - I wish you were, but he's not.
他真討厭,他今天沒來
He's really sick. He ain't comin' out today.
- 威莉,從那下來 - 這下子可好了
- Williams, take her down. - That's terrific.
- 三個月的工作化為烏有 - 大家走吧
- Three months of work down the tubes. - You're outta here, guys.
你在盤點存貨嗎？
So, what, are you taking inventory?
不是,我準備好打乒乓球
No, Mr. Jones. I'm getting ready to play Ping-Pong.
我要去工作了,你有什麼困難嗎？
I'm goin' to work, Mr. Jones. You got a problem with that?
- 工作? - 工作
- Work? - Work.
- 你儘量保持穩定 - 這是怎麼回事, 醫生?
- Try to hold as steady as you can. - What the hell is it, Doc?
-我要取些皮膚樣本 -給我吃藥
- I'm taking a little skin sample. - Come on. Give me something.
等一會,保持穩定
Just a second. Steady as you can.
我設法快點完事,行了
Try to do it as quick as I can. That's it. I got it.
穩住，穩住，小心
Steady, steady, steady. Easy, easy.
沒事的，別用手碰它
It's all right. Keep your hands off it.
按住這
Here. Hold that.
我要在顯微鏡下看清楚
I'm gonna take a look at this under the microscope.
22號貨櫃滿了
Container 22 is full, sir.
好,這個滿了便運走,換新的箱子來
Okay, this one's full up, so let's run her outta here and bring in a new one.
好的
You got it.
未知生物體? 別逗了
"An organism of unknown origin." No kidding.
告訴我些我不知道的
Tell me something I don't know.
給我個機會、這不是一年級的生物學、樣本完成並記錄
告訴我些我不知道的
Tell me something I don't know.
給我個機會、這不是一年級的生物學、樣本完成並記錄
我要個答案
該死的，來猜一猜
Goddamn it, take a guess.
沒頭緒
該死的，來猜一猜
Goddamn it, take a guess.
處理中
基因變異?
去外面好好工作, 貝基 我是說,貝克先生
Good work out there, Becky. I mean, Mr. Beck.
幹得不壞, 貝克先生
Not bad, Mr. Beck.
小意思
No harm done.
只要別稱我駭客
Just don't call me cracker.
打起精神來
Perk up, sport.
他怎會在八小時內死於皮膚發癢?
How can the guy die from a skin rash in eight hours?
戴上它 我想你檢驗他
Put this on. I want you to examine him.
- 我不是醫生 - 幹著，不需要你是醫生
- I'm not a doctor. - For this, you don't need to be.
好吧，大人
Oh, Lord.
我戴這個是因為你認為會傳染?
Am I wearing this 'cause you think it might be contagious?
我不知道，我也不知道是不是
I don't know if it is, I don't know if it isn't.
我什麼也不知道,也沒人知道
I don't know a damn thing. Neither does anyone else.
這些天我都在與海軍堛漫唹抾貑琱H交流
I've been going back and forth with Narragansett Naval all day.
向海洋醫療中心的專家諮詢...
Consulting with the best people in marine medicine...
他們都是病毒學上最好的專家
the best people in virology.
他們甚至不相信我描述的病徵
They don't even believe the symptoms I'm describing.
他們猜測，這只是一個猜測...
Their best guess, and that's all it is is just a guess...
在希克斯派克死前，
is that before Sixpack died, he was undergoing
發生了某些遺傳變異
some form of genetic alteration.
什麼引起遺傳變異？
Genetic alteration from what?
可能是許許多多事情
It could be a million things.
某些食物,空氣
Something in the food, the air.
希克斯派克上過那艘船,威莉也是
Sixpack went in that ship, and so did Williams.
我想檢驗其餘的船員
I want to examine the rest of the crew.
但我不想引起他們恐慌
But I don't want to create a panic, so until I get some answers
在找出答案前,別告訴大家希克斯派克的死訊
I don't think we should tell them that Sixpack is dead.
他皮膚怎麼回事？是皰疹還是麻疹？ 到底是什麼？
Skin condition? Herpes? Measles? What is it?
很難確切描述
It's a little difficult to describe.
天哪，這將是很糟糕的事情
Christ, it would be a hell of a thing
如果我染上了麻疹
if I went back up to the roof with a herpes thing.
我妻子怎麼說了都不會明白
My wife would never understand that at all.
我們用不著擔心這個,是嗎？
I don't think we have to worry about that, do we?
不,她不會明白
She wouldn't understand that at all.
她以為我出去鬼混的
She'd think I was down here screwing my head off or something.
穿上襯衣吧
Put on your shirt.
- 沒事吧 - 對，你很好
- It's all right? - Yeah, you're fine.
這些事是不必要的, 醫生
This whole thing is unnecessary, Doc.
我唯一知道的皮膚問題,就是種族白人
The only skin problem I can see is white people.
你為什麼戴著手套？
How come you're wearin' those gloves?
這不是彎腰的時候，是不?
It ain't bend-over time, is it?
- 出什麼岔子了嗎? - 沒有,我只想查看一些東西
- Anything wrong? - No, I just wanted to see something.
僅此而已
That's all.
你認為是和船上的事有關？
You think it has anything to do with going on that ship?
有可能,但若是這樣
Well, it's a possibility. But if that was the case
你便會有病徵,是嗎？
you'd be showing some symptoms, wouldn't you?
- 我沒事？ - 你很好
- I'm okay? - You're fine.
你真的沒事
No, really, you're fine.
好極了，謝謝 醫生
Great. Thanks, Doc.
你什麼意思,皮膚問題?
What do you mean, a skin problem?
皮膚起變化？
Your skin changes?
- 是的，變黑及起鱗片 - 什麼,像魚那樣?
- Yeah, it blackens. It gets scaly. - What, like a fish?
- 是的, 就像魚一樣 - 我只是開個玩笑, 醫生
- Yeah, like a fish. - I was justjoking, Doc.
你可以到外面去把衣服穿好
You can finish getting dressed now.
噢,褒曼，對不起,我去去就回
Oh, Bowman. I'm sorry. I'll be right back.
- 形態變異? - 變異？
- Generic alteration? - Genetic.
隨便了，你認為只局限於這船的船員?
Whatever. But you think it's restricted to this one crew member?
- 目前是的,不過 - 不過什麼?
- Well, so far, but... - But what?
到頭來如果又沒事怎麼辦？
What if it turns out to be nothing?
你說什麼啊？已經有一個人死了
What are you talking about? It's already killed one man!
但你沒證據說這是傳染病，對不?
But you have no proof that this disease is contagious, do you?
我們以前也曾判斷失誤過，對不，湯普生醫生?
And we've been wrong before, haven't we, Dr. Thompson?
瞧，瑪蒂,我認為你看錯了問題
Look, Martin, I think you're missing the point here.
我的船員有危險,這病徵我見過
My crew's in jeopardy. I've seen this disease.
而且我們也不是在海灘邊
And it's no day at the beach.
所以根據手冊上第539條
So by way of paragraph 539 of the manual
我命令你啟動醫療緊急程式，
I'm ordering you to start an emergency medical evacuation
並疏散礦坑堛漫狾酗H員
of all the personnel on the shack.
這由你決定,不過可惜的是
It's your call, but Unfortunately
我們沒法這麼快來接你們
we can't pick you up so soon.
離古巴海岸六百里處有颶風
There's a hurricane 600 miles off the coast of Cuba
可能吹向你們
possibly coming your way.
如果這樣,公司可不想讓員工的生命冒危險
And if it does, the company does not want to risk losing you folks.
你說什麼?
What are you saying?
你是說你不能按原定時間來接我們？
Are you saying you're not gonna pick us up at the scheduled time?
不會耽誤太久的
It shouldn't be a long delay.
好吧, 太久是多長時間? 一天？一周？
Well, What's a long delay? A day? A week? What?
十二小時,我們明早就可以確定
Twelve hours. We should know something first thing in the morning.
- 我會繼續與你聯絡的 - 你最好在那
- I'll keep you posted. - You better be there.
- 十二小時？ - 十二小時
- Twelve hours. - Twelve hours.
我保證
I promise.
褒曼，褒曼,你沒事吧?
Bow. Bow, are you okay?
我的天
Oh, my God. Come on.
你能來幫幫我們嗎？
Can you help us here?
- 讓我們把她放在這 - 來吧，小心點
- Let's put her here. - Come on. Take it easy.
沒事的
It's all right.
你不會有事的,好嗎? 我會去找醫生,好嗎?
You're gonna be all right, okay? I'm gonna go find Doc, all right?
嗨, 醫生?也許他和希克斯派克在一起
Hey, Doc? Maybe he's with Sixpack.
醫生? 嗨，你在這?
Doc? Hey, you in here?
希克斯派克?
Sixpack?
嗨,夥計,你在幹嘛?
Hey, man, how you doin'?
我們達成指標了, 夥計, 雖然不用謝你和你的狗，但我們辦到了
We made quota today, man, no thanks to you, you dog, but we made it.
你可能不信，但貝克幫了我們
You won't believe this, man, but Beck helped us out.
對,我們只是把褒曼送來這
Yeah, we just brought Bowman in, man.
她不太舒服
She don't look too good.
你明白,我希望你們患的不是傳染病
You know, I hope what you got ain't catchin'.
瞧, 我很抱歉
Hey, look, I'm sorry, man.
你回去再睡吧,好嗎?
You go on back to sleep, okay?
我一會再跟你談
I'll talk to you later, all right?
- 我要去查看下控制室 - 好的
- I'm gonna go check the control room. - Okay.
- 我很快就回來，行嗎? - 威莉, 拜託別走!
- I'll be back in a minute, okay? - Willie, please don't go!
請別離開我，我太難受了
Please don't leave me. I'm so sick.
噓，你會沒事的，別擔心
Shh. You're gonna be okay. Don't worry.
(Crying)
希克斯派克...
Sixpack...
希克斯派克?
Sixpack?
我的頭髮在掉
My hair's coming out.
你說什麼? 在醫務室?
Where'd you say? The infirmary?
對
Yeah.
褒曼?
Bowman?
我不明白了，我們剛把她留在那
I don't understand. We just left her here.
褒曼? 褒曼, 醫生來了!
Bowman? Bowman, it's Doc!
噢，天哪
Oh, man.
除此之外,我再沒什麼可告訴你...
Other than that, there's not much more that I can tell you about it...
你們當中沒有人有病徵
except that none of you have any of the symptoms.
是這疾病殺了褒曼？
And this disease, it killed Bow?
不
No.
不是，她是自殺的
No, she killed herself.
嘿，我們最好離開這兒
Hey, we're getting outta here just in time.
是的，不過我們還有一個麻煩
Yeah, well, that's a whole 'nother problem.
我們得等人來接，但可能有颶風在向這兒吹來.
We're on hold for the pickup. There's a hurricane rollin' into this sector.
- 颶風? - 是的,我們要延期十二小時
- A hurricane? - Yeah. We're delayed 12 hours.
十二小時？那我們怎麼辦？不能在這幹等12小時
Twelve hours? What're we gonna do? We can't stay here for 12...
- 那是什麼聲音? - 慢著,別亂動
- What was that? - Wait a minute. Hold on. Just stay put.
好嗎? 醫生
Okay? Doc.
噢，天哪
Oh, my God.
那是什麼東西？
What is this?
到底怎麼回事, 醫生?
What's goin' on, Doc?
- 好,威莉, 去開門 - 收到
- Okay, Willie, get the door. - Got it.
貝克
Beck.
合同上說過未經許可不得擅自棄置屍體
The contract states that you can't dispose of a body without authorization.
算了吧，你能不能別再拿合同來說事了？
Come on. Will you for once forget about the contract?
C區門要健康安全密碼 小心
Section C of the Health and Safety Code. Watch it.
威莉,開啟門鎖程式
Willie, program that lift lock.
我覺到有什麼東西在
Hey, I feel something.
你在說什麼？他們已經死了
What are you talkin' about? They're dead.
等會,我也覺到有什麼東西
Wait a minute. I feel something too.
- 我們走 - 有什麼活的東西在這
- Let's go. - Somebody's alive in here.
來吧，來吧
Come on. Come on. Come on.
好的,來吧,讓我們把它沖走，醫生
Alright, come on, let's flush it, Doc.
你說什麼"沖走它?" 我們說的可是些人
What do you mean "Flush it?" They're human beings we're talking about
- 看在上帝的面上，拜託! - 如果有人還活著怎麼辦?
- for God's sake! - What if one's alive?
- 那麼我們來默哀下? - 就這樣,來吧，醫生
- How about a moment of silence? - Let's do it, Doc.
上帝啊,他們還活著!
My God, they're alive!
- 抬起來 - 打開看看
- Get it up here. - Let's have a look.
褒曼
Bow.
- 別停! - 那該死的是什麼東西?
- Don't stop! - What the hell was that?
按那鈕!
Hit the button!
- 按那左邊的鈕! - 快從這出去!
- Hit the lift button! - Get outta there!
沖走那該死的東西!沖走它!
Flush the damn thing! Flush it!
貝克!
Beck!
這!
Come on!
噢，天哪!
Oh, God!
它朝這過來了，監視器鏡頭會沿途拍到在哪個房間，就是這樣
It's coming up now. That camera's gonna move into this room. That's it.
這像是病房或實驗室什麼的，停，往回倒
Some kind of sick bay or lab or something. Hold it. Run it back.
就這，停，現在放
That's it. Stop. Now move in.
看見沒?像是個人類頭骨，我不清楚
See? It looks like a human skull, but I don't know.
- 有點不對勁，它... - 比較大
- There's something about it. It's... - Bigger.
也許是有人在作怪，你看看那只手
Well, somebody's been screwing around. Just take a look at that hand.
- 你看那只手有多大 - 如果你說的是變異...
- Look at the size of it. - If you were tampering with genetics...
為何到了基本模式便停滯不前?
why stop with the base model?
為何不設法改變人類形態?
Why not try to alter the human form?
海底人,一個可以在水底生存的人
Homo aquaticus, a man who could live underwater. Think of the possibilities.
就像再生脫胎換骨
Regeneration.
可以抵抗嚴寒,壓力
The ability to withstand extreme cold, pressure.
你想想看，海底採礦,海底耕作
Just think of it. Undersea mining. Underwater farming.
下一步會怎樣?我的意思是,如果有一天我們再不需要飛機
So What's next? I mean, what if we run outta airplanes one day?
我們會怎樣?進化成像鳥一樣?
What are we gonna do? Just grow a whole bunch of bird people?
大自然規律不可違背
Natura no confundendo est.
我是說"不能對自然規律亂來"
Loosely translated: "Don't fuck with Mother Nature."
我最好該通知公司
I better let the company know.
你認為他們早已懷疑到了嗎？
Have you ever thought that they may suspect already?
是的，我想到過, 醫生
Yeah. I thought about that, Doc.
但我一直認為他們對員工也有責任
But I also like to think they got some kind of commitment to their people.
你這番話留在廣告活動上說吧
You can save that speech for your ad campaign.
這公司唯一在乎的就是金錢
This company's commitment is to the almighty dollar.
你想下,如果我們實情相告
If you think, based on what we've told them, that Tri-Oceanic
三大洋公司會只為了救我們，而冒在市場上受損的潛在風險嗎
is gonna risk exposing themself to potential market loss just to save us
在你的工作經歷上會是次大開眼界的
you're in for an eye-opening experience.
也許
Maybe.
也許會，我知道你的生活總是一團糟, 醫生
Maybe so. And I know your life's gone a couple of bad rounds, Doc.
但這不一定表示這公司就是一大垃圾堆
But it doesn't necessarily mean this whole company's one big bummer.
我認為我們在這能拿些東西
I think we got something here.
他媽的
Son of a bitch.
我拿不到，他們為什麼要把它放在伏特加里?
I don't get it. Why did they put it in the vodka?
因為那是實驗
It was an experiment, man.
我是說, 他們有意把藥物或其他什麼放進伏特加里
I mean, they put the drug or whatever it was in the vodka!
然後引人喝下去
They meant to trick them into takin' it.
這麼一來他們不知喝了什麼
That way, see, they didn't know what they were drinkin'.
可能他們在我們的咖啡堣]放了
I mean, with us, they would have put it in the coffee.
- 你想說什麼? - 來吧
- What are you talkin' about? - Come on, man.
你也知有些母親把蓖麻混進橙汁
You know how mothers put the castor oil in with orange juice?
引誘孩子不知不覺的喝下去
They trick the baby into drinkin' it so he don't know what he's drinkin.
這就是他們在做的,夥計!
That's the kind of shit they was doin', man!
愚蠢，他們可能把我們全害死
Fool. He could've got us all killed.
你的夥計們喝伏特加時可沒這麼神聖
You guys weren't so holy when you were shooting that vodka.
受害的可能是任何人
It could've been anyone.
好了, 高大強壯的女士，這事似乎麻煩到你了
Well, Miss High and Mighty, it doesn't seem to bother you none.
是的，是煩到了
Yeah, it bothers me.
你有你的處事方式，我也有我的
You deal with it your way. I'll deal with it mine.
你知道在格施塔德有個64平方英里的滑雪場嗎
You know that in Gstaad they have 64 square miles of ski slopes?
64平方英里呢
Sixty-four square miles.
在我們剛剛經歷了那些事，你怎麼還有心情坐這談滑雪
How can you sit there goin', "Shh, shh," after what we just went through?
另外，我已聽夠你談滑雪了
And another thing, man. I'm gettin' tired of hearin' about your goddamn skiin' OK?
夥計，你一點都不懂滑雪的事，人們可不會去西班牙滑雪的
You don't know shit about skiin', man. They don't ski in Spanish Harlem.
我們剛才所見的事又怎麼樣?
What about what we just saw?
就像威莉說的,我們各有處事方法
Like Willie said, you deal with it your way, and I'll deal with it mine.
- 難道沒人關心所發生的事嗎？ - 你想怎樣來對付它，啊？
- Doesn't anybody care what just happened? - What're you gonna do about it? Huh?
希克斯派克和褒曼死了
Sixpack and Bow are dead.
對所發生的事我也無能為力，難道你行嗎?
I can't help what happened. Can you?
我要去找些東西吃,還有誰要吃東西嗎？
I'm gonna go get somethin' to eat. Anybody want anything?
吃? 你還有心情吃東西？
Eat? After what we just went through?
颶風正朝這兒吹來
The storm's still holding its course.
還有這疾病，只有一個人染上了?
What about that disease? Still just the one crew member?
對,還只是一人
No change. Still just the one.
每個人都很緊張不安,你在幹什麼？
Hey, man, everybody's jumpy. What are you doin'?
找些黃油來做爆米花
Lookin' for butter for the popcorn.
聽著，你是要我自己一個人解決這個難題，還是怎麼的?
Look, Hazy, you gonna make me finish this puzzle by myself, or what?
我會的，你知道這要我花多長時間嗎？
I should. You know how long that took me?
許多許多個小時
Hundreds, thousands, millions of hours.
- 我去去就回 - 好，快點
- I'll be right there. - Okay. Hurry up.
(Hissing)
(Screaming)
該死!
Holy shit!
拜託，天哪, 救我！救我, 鐘斯!
Please, God, help me! Help me, Jonesy! Help me.
我去找人幫忙,很快回來,好嗎？
I'm gonna go get some help. I'll be right back, okay?
別離開我，鐘斯,不要離開我!
Don't leave me. Jonesy, don't leave me!
- 求你了 - 我很快回來
- Please. - I'll be back.
瞧! 它抓住了德休斯!待在這看好門
Look! It's got Hazy! Stay here and watch the door!
別放它出來,我去找醫生
Don't let him out! I'm gonna go get the doc.
我不想對她說褒曼的事
I didn't want to tell her about Bowman.
我聽瑪蒂說,我知道她胡說八道
I listened to Martin, and all my mind says "She's full of shit."
它抓住了德休斯!快來!
It's got DeJesus! Come on!
貝克,別進去，別碰任何東西
Beck, don't go in there. Don't touch anything!
德休斯! 柯布!
DeJesus! Cobb!
你該死的做了什麼？ 你該在看好門的
What the hell you doin'? You supposed to be watchin' the door!
沒有保護我才不會
I'm not gonna watch that thing without some protection.
- 那東西是我的朋友 - 你朋友已經不是人類了
- That thing is my friend. - Your friend is not human!
別吵了,住嘴!鐘斯! 讓我們去找他
Shut up, both of you! Jones! Let's go find him.
走吧，我們去找他 等下，威莉呢?
Okay? Come on. Let's go find him. Wait a minute. Where's Willie?
發生什麼事？
What's happening?
我的天,她在外面
My God, she's out there.
好吧. 鐘斯你跟我來
All right, look. Jones, you come with me.
醫生,你和柯布去檢查辦公室和宿舍，來吧
Doc, you and Cobb check your office and the dorm. Let's go.
威莉?
Willie?
嗨, 貝克
Hey, Beck.
噢，不，是她的圍巾
Oh, no. It's her scarf.
對不起,你們在這兒做什麼？
Oh, sorry. What are you doing here?
- 你該死的在這做什麼？ - 我在試著修好這些燈
- What the hell you doin'? - I've been trying to fix these lights.
發生了什麼?
What's going on?
殺死希克斯派克和褒曼的東西還在這
Whatever got Sixpack and Bowman is still here.
- 什麼? - 它剛抓了德休斯
- What? - Lt just got DeJesus.
說話啊，我們在和呆子說話
All right. We're talkin' turkey.
德休斯!嘿!
DeJesus! Hey!
醫生
Doc.
噢，天哪
Oh, my God.
血袋
The blood supply.
老天
Oh, my God.
它拿走了血袋
It got the blood supply.
(Screaming)
它在長，它要吃東西
It's growing. It's had a meal.
- 它吃血？ - 顯然是的
- It needs blood? - Apparently.
太棒了，你是說，我們中間有人是吸血鬼嗎
This is great. You're tellin' me we got a goddamn Dracula in here with us?
這就是為什麼那艘船上的人死了，它需要血
That's why that one on the ship was dead. It needed blood.
哪艘船？
What one on that ship?
有人要洩露你的小秘密了?
Somebody want to let the rank-and-file in on your little secret?
不管怎樣，這看起來就像遺傳變異
Whatever it is, it appears to be a genetic aberration.
- 別廢話 - 你要告訴我們什麼, 醫生?
- No shit. - What're you trying to tell us, Doc?
它有深海生物的各種特徵,有鱗，有鰓...
It has all the characteristics of deep-sea marine life: Scales, gills...
它不停地在再生，甚至在短暫的蟄伏期內
regeneration, even a period of dormancy.
而且它記得血庫在哪兒
But the fact that it remembered where that plasma was stored
似乎它還有其他物質
seems to imply that is has some other quality.
- 什麼? - 它能吸取受害者的智慧
- What? - Lt absorbs the intelligence of its victim.
智慧這個詞來描述可能不大準確
Intelligence may not be the right word.
別該死的咬文嚼字了, 醫生 你想說什麼?
The hell with semantics, Doc. What are you saying, now?
那東西有德休斯,希克斯派克，褒曼的部分智慧?
This thing is part DeJesus, part Sixpack, part Bowman, what?
我不太清楚，我只是猜的
I don't know. I'd just be guessing.
但我明白的是
But I do know this:
俄國人為了自保而弄沉了自己的船
The Russians deliberately sank that ship to protect themselves.
也許是為了保護我們
Maybe to protect us all.
好吧，是為了保護我們
Alright. Then I say we protect ourselves.
讓我們去逃生氣泡艙，趕快離開這該死的地方
Let's escape into those air bubbles and get the hell out of here.
去迎面碰颶風？
And hit the surface in the middle of a hurricane?
夥計，颶風會把氣泡艙打成碎片的
Man, that storm'd rip those bubbles to pieces.
- 他們永不會找到我們 - 我們根本沒有生還機會
- They'd never find us. - We wouldn't stand a snowball's chance in hell.
- 那我們該怎麼辦 - 聽著，我們還有一個機會
- So what are we gonna do? - Look, I think we got one shot.
只有一個，我們把它引到洗礦池堙A然後像洗礦那樣沖掉它
Just one shot. We lure it down into the swamp, flush it out just like the other.
我們該怎樣進行？
And how're we gonna do that?
那麼我們半小時後集合
So we rendezvous in the mess in 30 minutes.
柯布先生,對下時間，30分鐘
Mr. Cobb, synchronize 30 minutes.
- 馬克,聽到了嗎？ - 收到
- Mark. Got it? - Got it.
好的,我再說一次
Okay, so I'll run this by you again.
如果鐘斯和我三十分鐘後還回不到這食堂
If Jones and I aren't back here in 30 minutes in the mess,
不管有沒有颶風,你們都要進到氣泡艙離開這
hurricane or nothin', you get in those escape bubbles and haul ass.
- 明白嗎 - 明白
' Okay? ' Okay_.
- 讓我們來吧 - 都當心點
- Let's do it. - Be careful with this.
- 別擔心，我不會再放棄什麼的 - 保重
- Don't worry. I don't want to give up any more. - Take care.
我盡力而為
I'll do my best.
好的，來吧
Okay, let's go.
你知道嗎, 我以前很棒的
You know, I was quite good once.
我以前做了很多重要的事?
When I did something, it was important, you know?
我發明了幾種藥物還有專利
I developed drugs and techniques
世界各地的醫生每天都會用到
that're used every day by doctors all over the world.
- 這是有區別的 - 一直都是, 醫生
- Made a difference. - Lt still does, Doc.
這癢得要命
This itches like hell.
- 我還好 - 讓我看看
- I'm all right. - Let me have a look.
真的很癢
It really itches.
那因為它在痊癒
That's because it's healing.
我給你換藥,看能否使你舒服點
I'm gonna change that dressing, see if I can't make you more comfortable.
- 你要去哪, 醫生? - 醫務室
- Where are you going, Doc? - The infirmary.
不用任何保護?
Without protection?
- 你不該到外面去 - 她說的對
- You shouldn't go out there. - She's right, you know.
緊急逃生氣泡艙、準備啟動
啟動
(Muffled booming)
- 你聽到了嗎? - 聽到了
- You hear that? - I hear it.
我們走
Here we go.
- 脫下你的襯衣, 柯布 - 好的
- Take off your shirt, Cobb. - Sure.
我覺得很冷
I'm cold.
請救我
Help me, please.
哦，好的
Oh, yeah, sure.
醫生? 醫生!
Doc? Doc!
救我!
Help me!
怎麼回事?
What's happening?
救命!
Help!
醫生
Doc.
(Screaming)
- 貝克! 鐘斯! - 威莉!
- Beck! Jones! - Willie!
(Roaring)
- 威莉，快跑! - 跑!
- Willie! Run! - Run!
快從那離開!
Get over here!
威莉!
Willie!
(Screaming)
你怎麼樣，還好吧? 醫生和柯布在哪?
How are you doin'? All right? Where's Doc and Cobb?
- 它抓到了醫生 - 等會，它剛就在那
- It got Doc. - Wait a minute. It was just here.
- 我知道 - 等下，你看到它了?
- I know. - Wait a second. You saw it?
- 是柯布，它在他身體堶 - 慢慢說，你是說它們有2個?
- It was in Cobb. It was in him. - Slow down. There's two of them?
- 見鬼 - 好吧
- Shit. - All right.
- 你怎麼樣? - 還好
- How are you doin'? - Okay.
好，現在怎麼辦?
Okay, now what?
你對巨型海浪有什麼感受?
How do you feel about big waves?
我喜歡海浪
I love waves.
我們被困住了,逃生氣泡艙不見了
We're trapped. The escape bubbles are gone.
- 威莉, 那扇門 - 嘿,看這個
- Willie, the door. - Hey, look at this.
我非常清楚我的最後決定
"I am fully aware of the finality of my decision."
我希望我們的犧牲能使人類
It is my hope that our sacrifice will mean that the human race
永遠不知道這可怕的突變
"will never know this awful mutation."
- 這簡直就是我們得死刑令 - 是由那個好好醫生簽的字
- Our death warrant. - Signed by the good doctor.
去他的吧
Hell with it.
- 你在幹嗎? - 好了...
- What are you doing? - Well...
我要看看我們目前的情況有多糟？
I'm gonna find out just how far up Shit Creek we are.
- 謝天謝地你還活著。 - 你到哪去了?
- Thank goodness you're still alive. - Where you been?
嘿, 你們最好現在過來救我們，立刻!
Hey man, you better get your ass out here now and get us. Right now!
拜託，鐘斯,冷靜，我們還沒打算拋棄你
Please, Mr. Jones, calm down. We haven't deserted you.
當我們收到湯普生醫生的資訊後，我們自然很擔心你們
Naturally, after we received Dr. Thompson's message, we were concerned.
但我們絕不會拋下你們
But we never would have deserted you.
你們什麼時候能到?
When are you coming?
- 你說的十二個小時,還記得嗎? - 好吧，但有個壞消息
- You said 12 hours, remember? - Well, that's the bad news.
颶風正轉向你的方向，就現在，正在轉向...
The hurricane has turned your way. Right now, it's on a course of...
你該死的只管回答我的問題,你們什麼時候能來
Just answer the goddamn question. When are you coming?
- 希望48小時後能到吧 - 48小時?
- Hopefully, within the next 48 hours. - Forty-eight hours?
我明白你們一定很難接受
I realize you must have gone through hell...
混蛋，我們還在這遭難
Gone? Bitch, we're still here!
我又不能控制天氣，不過放心
I can't control the weather. Now, rest assured your SOS
你們發出的求救信號，海岸警衛隊和海軍都收到了
was received by the coast guard and the navy
我們會儘快趕往救援
and we will be responding at the earliest, safest opportunity.
別對我們信誓旦旦了
Just don't promise us nothin'.
當你們經歷這些後還對你們這麼說，的確有些荒謬
I realize this must sound ridiculous after what you've been through.
- 別廢話了 - 儘量去休息下吧
- No shit. - Now please try and get some rest.
該死的我們怎麼去休息？我是睡不著，你能睡著嗎?
How in the hell are we gonna get some rest? I can't sleep. Can you sleep?
- 去休息? - 省省吧
- Get some rest? - Save your breath.
- 該死，要48小時?沒門 - 我們別無選擇，有嗎?
- Damn. In 48 hours? No way. - We don't have much choice, do we?
我來告訴你怎麼辦，你們去休息，我來看著
I'll tell you what. I'll take a watch. You all try to get some rest.
我今生今世再也睡不著了
I ain't gonna never be able to sleep again. In life. Ever.
要求提交7月26日的天氣報告
"Request weather report, July 26."
- 沒有資料 - 來吧
- "Data not available." - Come on.
檔案已關閉
"Files Closed."
- 噢，夥計 - 他們知道了，對不?
- Oh, man. - They know, don't they?
是的，我想他們此刻大概在想怎麼對付我們
Yeah. I think they're just sittin' up there, decidin' what to do with us.
也許他們已經想好了
Maybe they already have.
- 你要找什麼？ - 我得看看投資得益如何？
- What're you looking for? - I'm seeing how my investment's doing.
當投資者們獲悉了一則悲慘的礦難事故消息後
"The stock of Tri-Oceanic Corp. Took a bath on world markets today"
三大洋礦業集團的股價今天在市場上大幅下跌
when news of a tragic mining accident was revealed to investors.
今天下午董事會成員立即被召集在紐約開了一次特別會議
The board of directors was immediately called into a special meeting in New York this afternoon.
發言人聲稱一場意外事故摧毀了第七號礦坑
A spokesperson revealed that the accident destroyed Shack Seven,
它位於大西洋第十區,靠近佛羅里達海岸
Atlantic Zone Ten, off the coast of Florida.
據消息說有八名礦工遇難，屍體全部失蹤
Eight miners are reported dead. All bodies are missing.
遇難的有史蒂芬·貝克,伊莉莎白·威廉姆斯，賈斯丁·鐘斯
Killed in the tragedy were Steven Beck, Elizabeth Williams, Justin Jones,
葛籣·湯普生醫生, 托尼·羅德羅, 布堮V特·褒曼,G.P.柯布, 巴茲·帕堣
"Dr. Glen Thompson, Tony Rodero, Bridget Bowman, G.P. Cobb, Buzz Parrish."
瑪蒂,你個賤人
Martin, you bitch.
歡迎加入,老闆
Welcome to the union, boss.
我們無足輕重
We're all expendable.
- 醫生, 我欠你5塊錢 - 5塊錢?
- Doc, I owe you five dollars. - Five dollars?
- 緊急警告 - 聽
- Emergency warning. - Listen.
- 內爆倒計時 - 供氧停了
- Countdown to implosion. - The air's stopped.
十分鐘倒數開始
Ten minutes and counting.
- 他們切斷了供氧管道 - 我們能修好嗎?
- They ripped open an air duct. - Can we fix it?
這建築物埵釭20英里長的管道，切口可能在任何地方
There are 20 miles of pipe in this building. They could've tapped in anywhere.
的確
That's true.
柯布，商業機密
Cobb. Job security.
A走廊的氣閘有雜音,是嗎？
It's that rattle that duct in Corridor A.
沒錯，它顯示問題出在哪里
You got it. It's showin' us where it is.
- 它能把我們吸出去 - 不費吹灰之力,對不?
- It's drawin' us out. - Lt didn't waste any time, did it?
你不能從那出去，這正是它所希望的
You can't go out there. That's what it wants.
好吧,如果我們在這堨╞h足夠的空氣，內壓會下降，然後會收縮
Yeah, well, if we lose enough air in here, the internal pressure will drop, and crunch.
是內爆,寶貝
Implosion, babe.
慢著，你們以為我會留在這媔?
Wait a minute. You don't think I'm staying here?
內爆倒數9分鐘
Nine minutes to implosion.
- 在這! - 就這嗎?
- It's over here! - Ls that it?
是的
Yeah.
- 它走了! - 空氣流失的速度比我想像的要快
- It's going! - We're losin' air faster than I thought.
- 走! 拿著 - 別在那待太久
- Go! Here. - Don't spend all day down there.
別擔心，我不會的
Don't worry. I won't.
讓我們動手吧
Let's do it.
內爆倒數8分鐘
Eight minutes to implosion.
- 噢，不，該死的! - 我們能修好嗎?
- Oh, no. Damn! - Can we fix it?
或許我們可以堵住它，去關掉其他地方? 想想辦法，夥計!
Can we block it off, maybe shut it down someplace else? Think, man!
快啊
Come on.
- 你在胡想什麼?難道我想死嗎? - 我們不會死的,我們會活下去
- What do you think? I wanna die? - We're not gonna die, man, we're gonna live.
現在想想!我們該怎麼辦?
Now think! What are we gonna do?
- 我怎麼知道? - 你瞭解這礦坑!
- How should I know? - You know this shack!
- 我不知道,我不知道! - 來吧! 這礦坑就像是你的家啊，夥計!
- I don't know, I don't know! - Come on! This shack's your home, man!
洗礦池，他們在那有個後背的氧氣閥，如果我們...
The swamp. There's a backup air valve at the swamp. If we...
醫生
Doc.
- 什麼? - 我剛看見醫生了
- What? - I just saw Doc.
不, 鐘斯，讓我們趕快離開這
No, Jones. Let's get outta here.
來吧
Come on.
內爆倒數7分鐘
Seven minutes to implosion.
- 小心! - 看著點!
- Look out! - Watch out!
威莉! 威莉!
Willie! Willie!
- 你行嗎? - 我想我們做到了!
- Did you get it? - I think we did it!
- 我不知道! - 快點!
- I don't know! - Hurry!
快走! 門要關了!
Move it! The door's closing!
另一扇門也要關了!
The other door's closing!
威莉, 快出去! 快出去!
Willie, get out! Get out!
- 照著它! - 小心!
- Torch it! - Careful!
鐘斯! 它卡住了!
Jones! It's jammed!
鐘斯,檢查下門! 威莉, 從這出去!威莉!
Jones, check that door! Willie, get outta here! Willie!
- 門要關了! - 抓著門!
- The door's closing! - Get that door!
走! 走！快走！
' Go! - Go! Go! Go'
內爆倒數6分鐘
Six minutes to implosion.
來啊!
Come on!
貝克!
Beck!
抓住我的手!
Grab my hand!
內爆倒數5分鐘
Five minutes to implosion.
抓住! 來啊!
Grab it! Come on!
走! 來吧!
Go! Come on!
你抓住
You got it.
來啊!
Come on!
貝克!
Beck!
- 讓我來幫他!讓我來! - 鐘斯!
- Let me help him! Let me go! - Jones!
桌上的手鋸!
The handsaw on the table!
加油!
Come on!
- 鐘斯, 救救他! - 退後!
- Jones, help him! - Stay back!
內爆倒數4分鐘
Four minutes to implosion.
沒有氧氣
There's no air.
這門卡住了
The door's jammed!
那氣閥! 它太燙了! 我拿不住它
The air valve! It's too hot! I can't get to it!
- 算了! 去拿潛水服! - 潛水服? 你瘋了嗎?
- Forget it! Get the suits! - The suits? You crazy?
威莉, 拿上浮力袋!
Willie, bring the lift bags!
- 我們怎麼樣到水面上去? - 就這樣
- How're we gonna get to the surface? - Like this.
我們把充氣速度加快三倍，我們就會像氣球樣升上水面
We'll triple the inflation ratio. We'll float to the top like a balloon. Go!
好吧,讓我們讓他們瞧瞧，穿上潛水服
Okay, let's hook 'em up. Get in the suits.
- 那你呢? - 把潛水服給我
- What about yours? - Just get in the suit.
內爆倒數3分鐘
Three minutes to implosion.
貝克, 來吧!
Beck, come on!
走!
(Screeching)
Let's go!
我們在水面上見
See you topside.
穿上你的潛水服!
Get into your suit!
貝克,穿上潛水服!
Beck, get into the suit!
貝克,別犯傻!
Beck, don't be a fool!
內爆倒數2分鐘
Two minutes to implosion.
救我
Help me.
我的天，是德休斯
My God. DeJesus.
殺了我
Kill me.
見鬼!
Shit!
(Screeching)
噢，該死!
Oh, shit!
內爆倒數1分鐘
One minute to implosion.
(Screeching)
你成功了!
You made it!
基地呼叫海岸警衛隊1437號救援直升機
Base to Coast Guard Rescue Chopper 1437.
再搜索一次區域後返回基地
Make one more attempt in search area and return to base.
- 鐘斯? 鐘斯! - 鐘斯.
- Jones? Jones! - Jones.
- 那該死的颶風呢? - 你還好吧?
- So where's the goddamn hurricane? - You all right?
- 我做到了 - 是的
- I made it. - Yeah?
是的, 我沒事，我很好，都很好，真的
Yeah, I'm fine. I'm all right. I'll be all right. Okay.
基地呼叫1437號救援直升機 有什麼發現嗎?
Base to Rescue Chopper 1437. Any visual contact?
- 沒有 - 返回基地
- Negative. - Return to base.
太冷了
It's cold.
- 嘿! - 這!
- Hey! - Here!
- 在這! - 把最後個照明彈給我
- Over here! - Give me that last flare.
前面有閃光
There's a flare straight ahead.
- 鐘斯! 看! - 是直升機
- Jones! Look! - Chopper.
- 鯊魚! - 在哪?
- Sharks! - Where are they?
- 靠近了! - 跟緊
- Too close! - Stay close.
跟緊!
Stay close!
今天真是糟糕透了
Talk about having a bad day.
- 救命! - 對了!過來!
- Help! - Yes! Come on!
- 天哪! - 威莉!
- Jesus! - Willie!
- 把那些人拉上來! - 走!
- Get those people up! - Go!
- 手抓緊! - 離開這!
- Grab a hand! - Get outta here!
它抓住了鐘斯!
It's got Jones!
貝克! 回來!
Beck! Come back!
不要! 自己救自己吧!
Don't! Save yourself!
貝克!
Beck!
回來!
Come back!
張大嘴，狗娘養的
Say "Aah," motherfucker!
讓我們離開這!
Let's get outta here!
救援直升機現在返回停靠港平臺
Helicopter 405 heading back to platform P.O.C.
他們不會想與這事扯上任何關係的，你知道嗎
They don't want anything else to do with it, you know?
貝克!
Beck!
你成功了!
You made it!
回到三大洋公司沒人會相信的
No one back at Tri-Oceanic believed me.
但我一次都沒想放棄過你，你感覺怎樣?
But I never gave up on you once. How do you feel?
好多了
Better. A lot better.
? anoXmous   @ https://thepiratebay.se/user/anoXmous